(upbeat music)
- You have a disability
insurance claim with Prudential.
Here's three secrets they're
not going to tell you.
I'm John Tucker, I'm
a disability attorney,
and I've been fighting
Prudential for my clients
for nearly three decades.
There's three things that come up
that my clients never knew about
that I think you should know about.
First, Prudential is going to use doctors
in the background that you're
never going to talk to.
They're going to review your file
and give Prudential opinions
that they'll rely upon to deny your claim.
Those doctors may even call your doctors
to have conversations about you,
that you won't find out
about until after the fact.
Tell your doctors not to talk to them,
and to ask for any questions
to be sent in writing.
Second, Prudential can be notorious
for taking too long to decide claims.
Group disability claims
have certain deadlines
that apply to them.
At the initial claim level
and at the appeal level,
there's different periods of time
that the insurance company can take
to decide the claim or decide the appeal.
Prudential won't tell you
what those deadlines are,
and then they'll take too much time.
But in reality, if they
take too much time,
you actually can go to the
next step in the process.
Sometimes that's filing a lawsuit,
and that's to your benefit,
but they won't tell you you
have the option to do that.
Finally, beware of Prudential
cherry-picking information
from your records that
helps them and hurts you.
What that means is they'll
reach into your records
and pull out the facts
that help them deny you,
but they won't pull out the facts
that explain why you're disabled,
your symptoms, your
limitations, your restrictions.
They'll ignore those.
So when you get a decision
letter from Prudential,
oftentimes you'll read it and
think, who is this person?
Where are all the facts about me?
Didn't they read my records?
If you've been denied by Prudential,
give me a call at the
number on your screen below.
I represent people just like
you all over the United States,
from Florida to Alaska,
in these group disability insurance cases.
Thanks for watching, I'm John Tucker.
(upbeat music)